[theme music playing]
GENIE, MAKE A WISH
[phone vibrates]
PLEASE RETURN YOUR ID
AND YOUR LOCKER AND BUILDING KEYS
Gu Bo-gyeong, I'm holding you
responsible for this. You're fired!
What will you do
about our branch's average balance?
Fuck! [sighs]
[Da-jin] A genie?
That's nonsense.
Our channel went viral
because you found that corpse.
Yeah, and the genie is the one
who helped me find the corpse.
I'm being serious!
Otherwise, how could I possibly
have found that corpse?
You have to believe me.
We only have two chances left, Da-jin.
We're both SKY grads.
We need to rack our brains and figure out
how to turn our lives around, okay?
[groans]
If it's a wish, could we wish
to inherit a conglomerate fortune?
[sighs] Why inherit it? We could
just become the conglomerates.
Hold up. How much
is the richest person in Korea worth?
Do we really need that much?
It's not like we're building an empire.
Say we have two kids.
If we fund their studies abroad
and a home for when they marry,
that's billions already.
What about retirement?
You're right. You can never have too much.
But are you sure there are no conditions?
In any fables with spirits,
the moral is always
"what goes around comes around."
"Pigs get fat, hogs get slaughtered."
What if there's a price?
[sighs]
-It would be nice if we could ask.
-Hey!
What if the genie answers
and counts it as a wish?
[gasps] You're right.
[sighs, clicks tongue]
Then how about
we think about it separately
and each get to use one wish?
What?
-But… why would I do that?
-Uh--
[scoffs] I wouldn't have told you
if we were going to do that.
Uh, we're a married couple,
so isn't it a given?
We can make money,
but some things money can't buy.
What are you thinking about?
Wishing for Dad to be cancer-free.
[groans] Come on, we have modern medicine.
Why would you wish
for something like that?
Money would solve everything.
My dad has terminal liver cancer.
Terminal means there's no hope.
Come on, it's not like
he's on his deathbed or anything.
Check out our views.
We'll be generating income in no time,
so let's just wait three months.
We'll just save the wish for now, okay?
Hey, Ko Yeong-hyeon.
Fuck you!
[clacking, thudding]
[soft tense music playing]
[breathing deeply]
-[yells in frustration]
-[clatters]
[breath trembling]
[Shadi] Khalid!
Khalid!
[in Arabic] I saw Iblis!
I saw him bringing humans to ruin.
It was truly a sight to behold, Father.
Tell me what you did.
Did you hurt the girl?
I feel no pain in this body,
nor do I feel out of breath.
But I do not have power like Iblis.
I have lost my ability to weave,
so what am I to do now
with this immortal body?
-[tense music playing]
-[Shadi breathing heavily]
[in Korean] The end is near!
You foolish humans!
Judgment day is approaching!
Angels from the sky alert us!
Heed me when I say…
[sighs] I'll let it slide today.
I have a lot on my mind.
Then you shall all be saved.
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
You said I stole a feather of yours
before I was locked up.
Again with your damn feather talk.
I don't know about it.
Well, I do. I know what I did with it.
I wrote some things.
On the floors and columns,
all over my lamp.
You figured that out?
Yes, but I'm not sure
when I could have done it.
Nor do I remember.
[Ka-young] So please
make sure we are punished.
You and I both.
That final wish Ki Ka-young made
was fulfilled.
Right?
He brought Ki Ka-young back to life
to carry out that final wish,
and I was reunited
with the reincarnated Ki Ka-young.
Am I wrong?
If my fury was enough to level a city…
HABIBTI
…it must mean I had lost a loved one.
I'd lost Ki Ka-young.
I must have loved her.
-Isn't that right?
-So what?
Are we playing bingo? What's your point?
About Ki Ka-young's lifespan.
You must be mad.
How much is left?
I beg you.
Tell me so I can prepare.
All because of a lowly human!
Have you learned nothing
from Shadi's fate?
Of course not.
Why else would I be doing everything I can
not to kill the immortal one?
Shadi loves that boy enough
to die for him,
and because he loves him,
the pain cuts deep.
You arrogant shaytan.
If you're so curious, pluck out my eyes
to see for yourself. Go ahead.
I wonder why he keeps
forgiving a bastard like you.
Who shall stand in the day of judgment?
Who will walk the path to salvation?
[breath trembling]
[crows cawing]
[Irem sighs]
[door opens and closes]
I was gathering intel on the immortal one.
I sensed that your intentions
were aligned with the immortal one.
The half-spirit is clawing his way up,
not knowing his place,
while Iblis and Ki Ka-young are edging
closer to the truth of their past lives.
And now, even my mythical beast
is totally missing the mark?
What now, Irem?
If you could just…
point me in the right direction--
What do you think I'm doing now?
Listen carefully.
No, wait. You can't hear, can you?
[chuckles]
Watch carefully.
The half-spirit will use Shadi
and plunge the world into sleep once more.
When that day comes,
there is something you must do.
That's all you need to do.
Am I understood?
Yes, Master.
[beeping]
-[chimes]
-[Heung-rye] Hmm?
These brats.
ELDEST
Hey, I've brought over some side dishes,
but your door won't seem to open.
I must be entering the wrong code.
[son] I told you not to come.
You know my wife's gone on a cruise.
That's why I cooked you food.
I'll just pop it inside--
[son] Just leave it at the door.
My wife doesn't want anyone
who's not family in the house.
You rotten bastard!
Aren't I family to you?
Am I a stranger? Am I?
You little…
[indistinct chatter]
-Stop eating and get peeling.
-[all laughing]
You're back early
from visiting your son, the judge.
Yes.
He kept asking me to stay over,
saying he'd send me on a cruise,
but I couldn't be bothered,
so I just came back.
How lucky you are. [chuckles]
[cell phones chime]
Mm? What is this?
OH PAN-GEUM
[Pan-geum] I think I'll be going
farther away than Hawaii.
Please take good care of my Ka-young.
Where's she off to now?
Her daughter must be
treating her incredibly well.
If it's farther away than Hawaii,
how nice must it be?
What's so great about being flown around
at a ripe old age? What a bother!
Hawaii? That old place?
I could go tomorrow if I wanted to.
My eldest son is a judge, and my youngest
is an executive at a major conglomerate.
And my grandchildren are all geniuses.
Just look at Ok-nam.
She abandoned her entire life
and ran away because of her child.
If anyone thinks they did a better job
at raising their kids than me,
come on out, I say!
Of course. Right you are!
-We all know. We all do.
-[everyone chuckles]
AN BOK-JA
[Bok-ja] Don't worry about Ka-young,
and send us some photos of the nice place.
[sighs] I wonder
where Ok-nam has gotten to.
She even changed her number.
-What is that smell? Is it chicken soup?
-Yes.
Tell that tall fellow to come too.
[grunts softly]
I hope you'll continue to get along
with my dear Ka-young.
Don't fight, and you mustn't leave her.
If she acts all prickly,
just be gentle with her.
[Iblis] Mm-mm.
-The drumsticks are always mine.
-Goodness me.
Just play nice and share. Hmm.
What's yours is his, even a bean.
For better or worse,
until death do you part.
Then give him beans.
The drumsticks are mine.
You brat!
Just let him have one today!
I'm doing all of this for a reason.
What reason?
The drumsticks are mine, so why?
-Don't you dare touch my…
-[rooster crowing in background]
-[cutlery clatters]
-Come here.
-You come here.
-[Mi-ju sighs]
-I said to come here.
-I said no.
[Mi-ju sighs]
Do you want to die?
[dramatic music playing]
-I'd rather not.
-Don't talk back!
Don't ask questions!
-I said not to talk back.
-I said not to ask questions!
[Ka-young] Stop copying me!
This level of chemistry
is good enough for me.
-[Ka-young] Get over here!
-[Iblis laughs]
[Ka-young screaming and grunting]
Mm. Seeing as this word comes up the most,
is this habibti? "My love"?
What? Right, yes. It is.
-You don't even remember, but this is me?
-Mm?
There's a 50-50 chance it's me or Jinniya.
Shouldn't you have cleared up
those doubts before we kissed?
If this happens to be Jinniya,
you will die for exploiting my hard labor.
So hurry and find your memories.
[Iblis] I've found one.
It says, "Every night you make a garment
to wear when you return to Goryeo."
A garment?
Hmm. I guess I must have liked
needles back then too.
-[Iblis] Hmm?
-[wrench clatters]
Where is Khalid's name?
Here and here.
Why?
Because, in Korea,
it's unlucky to write names in red.
This brat.
If this is when he started preparing,
then we're losing on all fronts.
We're completely winning at one thing.
No matter how much information Khalid has,
you'll be the one making the wish.
Let's get out of here.
From now on,
you and the lamp are inseparable.
You want me to carry it around?
Like a portable
curry pot.
That's believable, right?
That's why…
Here.
I saw people carrying these things around.
-Not bad at adapting.
-Mm-hmm.
I wonder how much time we have left.
On that note,
listen carefully to what I say now.
I'm sure Khalid will use Shadi again
to try to tie me up.
If that moment comes, and I am tied up,
you must use your final wish
to save yourself.
You must make a righteous wish. Got it?
It seems you've decided where you'll go.
-Well, I'll never let you go.
-[chuckles]
I knew that wouldn't work. [chuckles]
[Yeong-hyeon] By the way,
do psychopaths really not feel love?
You know, being ready
to give your life for someone else.
I would be willing
to kill for someone else.
-Doesn't that count as love?
-[key clacks]
Hey, Choi Da-jin. Look at this!
That old interview we did
with the psychopath is blowing up again!
It's trending at number nine! [laughs]
There's even a meme in the comments…
"I worked late instead of my manager.
Doesn't that count as love?"
"I binged on food instead of my boyfriend.
"I only ate the tails
of the fish-shaped pastry for you."
Only the tails? That's mental. [laughs]
This is fucking hilarious.
So what will we do
about the wishes?
You're talking about that again?
[sighs wearily]
I'm so sick of this.
Let's just enjoy the moment
for a while! [sighs]
[sighs]
No.
Let's just get a divorce.
What?
You said you had two wishes left, right?
Give me one of them as alimony.
A divorce?
[sighs] Have you gone insane?
Hey.
Frankly speaking, they're my wishes.
Who do you think you are?
Right. This is how
you really feel, isn't it?
Son of a bitch.
What? Hey, what did you
just call me? Son of a bitch?
This person really is Oh Pan-geum?
That's right, Oh Pan-geum.
The third daughter
of the lady from Bukcheon.
She was the prettiest thing in Hadong
and moved to Seoul when she got married.
That smile is her, all right.
Her husband was from Chungcheong-do.
Last I heard,
both their daughters got married.
Let me take a look.
My word! This was when
she was a young thing.
But why are you looking for her anyway?
What is it? Did Pan-geum here die?
No, she's very healthy.
[woman sighs in relief]
That's good to hear.
[Min-ji exhales]
[exhales]
[Ka-young] I'm not quite sure
what he does for a living.
He mostly tells me to make a wish.
Holy smokes, my teeth must have
gotten younger too.
Don't ask me anything about those two.
My deal?
[Ka-young] One thing I know for certain
is that he isn't human.
If I can't ask anything…
and he isn't human
and asks people to make wishes…
[laughing]
[exclaims]
I'm so stunned, all I can do is laugh.
Why? Just wear them out.
I just want to buy you something.
Wear these and go wherever you want to go.
Wherever that may be,
I'm sure it'll be the right path.
Okay?
[sniffles]
If Mi-ju…
[sniffles] …is actually Grandma…
[sobbing]
[liquid dripping]
[Pan-geum] Ka-young.
This is the soybean paste jar.
Once every month, open the lid
to check for mold growing on the surface
beneath the top salt layer
and for signs of bugs.
[sighs]
[inhales, sighs]
[Pan-geum] When the weather is nice,
leave the lid open so it gets some sun.
This is the soy sauce jar.
[crying]
If you happen to see
any white patches of mold,
scoop them away,
give it a good boil, and pour it back in.
[sniffles]
[crying]
-[bowl clangs]
-[sighs]
That means I'll be fine
until next spring.
That's good enough.
People die of accidents or illness.
It wouldn't be all that strange
to die at this age anyway.
Oh, my. You're up already?
You should sleep in on your day off.
I need to go to the workshop.
But, Grandma, why do you keep
looking at that tree?
What are you doing?
Thinking about whether to fix it.
But from here,
I have the point of view
of a corpse buried in a hole.
You sure have a way with words.
[wind blowing]
Would this mean we're buried together?
You're going to make things
this easy for me?
Should we go for a carpet ride tomorrow?
You can.
I'm going to Seoul with Grandma tomorrow.
You ride your carpet
and fix the roof.
Why Seoul?
Because I want Grandma to have
some ordinary memories of me.
All right.
I have one of those to make too.
[gentle music playing]
-[rapid clicking]
-[Sang-hyeok exclaiming]
[character groans]
-[whimpering]
-Sweet! A KO win!
You little…
I need to go home now.
Hey, that's not fair.
I haven't won a single game yet.
You should go home soon too, mister.
There's no place like home.
That sure doesn't sound like you.
-Did you buy a house, by any chance?
-That's not funny.
You can't tell anyone this,
-but an angel granted my wish.
-[chuckles]
Mom's boyfriend disappeared.
It's time I cut back on arcade games
so my mom doesn't worry.
I didn't expect this kind of fallout.
Kim Sang-hyeok!
It's been really fun.
And you're my bro.
Never forget that.
What's with you?
I said I'd cut back.
I didn't say I'd quit entirely.
See you tomorrow.
[chuckles softly]
-[thuds]
-[Mi-ju sighs]
[sighs] You're not going?
Why not?
It's the department store.
The new winter collection's out.
-I have a lot of clothes.
-[thuds]
I have plenty to last me
until next February.
Instead…
let's go somewhere else.
Where exactly?
You wanted to come here?
Why?
Because I want to be pretty
in your memories.
Don't I look pretty? Don't I look cute?
Aren't I just to die for?
In my memories?
Why does it seem like
she has the same idea as me?
-Smile.
-[camera shutter clicks]
-[chuckling] Like this.
-[camera shutter clicking]
-[whimpers]
-Hurry and do this!
[camera shutter clicking]
Like this? Maybe?
-[camera shutter clicks]
-All right. [giggles]
[camera shutter clicks]
[Mi-ju chuckles]
Oh, boy!
How pretty.
Why do people even do this?
Why not? It's so much fun.
Let's have coffee and enjoy ourselves
just a little longer.
Go and buy me something sweet, all right?
-Fine.
-Great.
[chuckles] Goodness me.
[chuckles]
[chuckles and sniffles]
[sighs]
Half the lights on your sign are out.
Trying to tell the world you're single?
I saw that too.
I smell gamja-tang.
It must be Wednesday.
I got it to go, though,
from a different place.
Let's eat.
I thought you'd get mad at me.
This is your routine.
CHEONGPUNG VILLAGE HALL
[intriguing music plays]
Oh. Grandma? How is Hawaii?
Ka-young is well.
Have you tried the coconut shrimp yet?
That sounds delicious.
Bullshit.
She's not somewhere nicer.
She's still in Hawaii.
[Min-ji laughs]
[Mi-ju sighs]
I'm going to stop holding
the ancestral rites now.
This is the last time.
Why?
We've already done enough.
When I die,
don't bother with any rites.
Don't do a thing.
Cremate me and scatter my ashes somewhere.
Leave it and go now.
It's a 12 o'clock flight, right?
It's at 11:45.
I've told Mr. Park to come,
so stay close to him.
I'll be back soon, okay?
All right. Go on.
[Iblis] I'm not sure what I wished for,
but I think it led to a very grim end.
So I'm scared.
[soft scraping]
[in Arabic] Excuse me, ma'am.
You've been rubbing this lamp
for three hours now.
It's only right that you buy it.
It's yours for 1,000 dirhams.
[in English] I cannot speak Arabic.
[in Arabic] How about a discount?
[Chang-Sik in Korean] Status update.
Keeping a close watch. No worries here.
[Ka-young] Thank you.
-[honking]
-[tires screech]
[man speaking in Arabic] What?
What do you want? What?
[suspenseful music playing]
TISAH
[people gasp]
[man grunts and groans]
[panting]
CONSULATE EMERGENCY HOTLINE
[sighs]
[breath trembling]
Would you go easy on the rubbing?
So you were avoiding me.
So what if I was?
When will you drop the attitude?
You'll be lucky to hit 100.
You recognized me the moment you saw me.
You called me the "bitch from back then."
Back when, in what time, was I that bitch?
Tell me everything you know.
This is my first wish.
Silly girl, what the hell are you saying?
I cannot grant things like wishes.
Only Iblis can do that.
Then I'll ask you very nicely.
What's with your smile?
The thing with Iblis is,
his mere presence makes us feel pathetic.
He stood at the front lines in the war…
[water gurgling]
[Jinniya] …and he saved us
from the angels.
All of us bowed our heads to you humans,
but he adamantly refused
and wound up in hell.
So to think the death of a mere human
made him level an entire city…
I couldn't wrap my head around it.
And that was me?
Yes, it was you.
You swept an entire city away
with gold rain. The bitch from back then.
Gold rain?
It was a dazzling and beautiful hell.
It was the rage of Iblis.
Why is his rage gold?
I don't know.
You don't know?
I don't want to know.
Why do you think Iblis has no memories?
Right, I'm sorry.
If you're sorry, never come back here.
This cancels out the time I danced for joy
when Muttalib killed you.
Go.
So the jerk who killed me…
Thank you.
By any chance,
has Iblis ever called you habibti?
Has anyone ever thrown water on you?
So it was me.
[thunder rumbling]
[thunderclap]
[pop music playing over speakers]
-[sighs]
-[Sade] Irem! Irem!
[panting]
[sighs]
Why did you ask to see me?
I just rolled out of bed.
Take a seat.
Sure.
I don't know the details,
but I have a feeling
there's more going on than we know.
When that day comes,
there is something you must do.
No cotton candy,
and you're already talking like that.
What could be going on?
You and I are both our masters' servants.
So if there comes a time
when you need to make a choice,
do so as your master's mythical beast.
I'll decide as I should too. Got it?
I came all dressed up.
What an odd way for you to dump me.
Didn't you just roll out of bed?
Your ears are showing.
I sleep like this.
-What are those?
-How cute.
-[woman] Buy me some.
-[man] Sure, let's get them.
MY CHANNEL
SKY FARM LIFE
[exhales]
NEW PASSWORD: 1 GENIE WISH IS MINE!
[keyboard clacking]
[suspenseful music playing]
PASSWORD CHANGED
[mouse clicking]
YOUR CHANNEL HAS BEEN DELETED
Hey, Choi Da-jin!
Hey, what's wrong with our channel?
Can you access it?
Damn it, the channel got deleted!
What the hell is going on?
Do you think someone reported us?
This will be the death of me, damn it.
No.
I just deleted it.
What? Are you insane?
Do you know what I did
to get all those subscribers?
Have you gone insane?
Hey!
You said to separate
what's yours and mine.
I made this account under my name.
If the wishes are yours,
this YouTube channel was always mine!
Wow, you're completely insane!
Hey, cut the bullshit.
I built it up when I found the corpse!
Whatever.
Get the genie here in front of me.
If we don't act in two weeks,
it's gone forever.
Consider it carefully.
Only I can restore the account.
Seriously, what you just did right now,
you better not fucking regret it later.
[breath trembling]
This is my second wish.
Make it so that Da-jin doesn't remember
a thing I told her about the wishes.
Make her forget
every single detail.
Right now, damn it.
[Iblis] Hey. For starters,
it's been fulfilled.
I was halfway across the Gobi Desert
when you called me.
This is just text,
but you can hear me, can't you?
A deep, velvety voice?
Did you think of a final wish
to make now too? Even if so, think more!
Be grateful I'm giving you the chance,
and don't use words
like "right now" or "hurry." Understand?
I told you to carry the lamp.
I was in a hurry,
so I left it at the hotel.
I thought I might recall something,
but no luck.
Man.
You scared me.
Hug me tighter.
It might help me recall something.
What is it you want to recall?
Muttalib from the sign over there.
Or the recurring villain, Khalid.
Or the joy or sorrow
that you and I felt in our past lives?
[chuckles]
This seems strategic.
You're mistaken. Hug me tighter!
[Iblis grunts softly]
[somber music playing]
[Iblis gasps]
You…
You're dressed strangely today.
Your hair is shorter too.
Are we ready to leave?
We're leaving?
[chiming]
You're here, so why would I?
Did I have a new master?
You seem a little odd today.
Muttalib is your master.
He must finally be ready
to make his final wish.
That means we really are
leaving tonight, right?
For Goryeo.
Muttalib was my new master?
[rumbling]
[Ka-young] What's wrong?
Hey.
Snap out of it.
There is a chance that…
I never managed to get you to Goryeo.
I think that's the reason my sword
is stuck over there.
What are you saying?
Oh?
You recalled something?
[scoffs] It actually worked?
Come here. Let's trade places.
[Ka-young sighs calmly]
[Iblis exhales]
[exhales]
[Heung-rye] I feel just the same,
so when exactly did I get so old?
Oh, my, it's you!
You came back without a word?
When did you get here?
Hello.
Good heavens,
I was so sure it was Pan-geum.
I must have been mistaken.
Never you mind.
[Mi-ju chuckling nervously]
Why the hell is she weeding a field
that isn't even hers?
[Mi-ju chuckles nervously]
[breathing heavily]
Wait a moment.
OH PAN-GEUM
[automated voice] The person you've called
is currently unavailable.
-Please leave a message after the beep.
-[inhales]
The more I think about it,
the stranger it all gets.
She sends texts
and talks with Min-ji on the phone,
so why did she only cut us off?
Yesterday was the anniversary
of her old man's passing.
So who did the ancestral rites?
[suspenseful music playing]
Huh?
That tramp was getting groceries
for the ancestral rites table!
Goodness me.
[classical music playing over speaker]
[Iblis sighs] I thought you'd say
the observation deck.
I don't want to stand
on the edge of anything anymore.
So why did you express
your rage with gold?
It was a dazzling and beautiful hell.
It was the rage of Iblis.
Do rage and gold even go together?
Gold? What do you mean by that?
Pointless if you don't remember.
Let's move on.
Either way, we knew each other
during those lost 20 years.
A 28-year-old you definitely existed
by my side. [clicks tongue]
-But Muttalib means "foreigner."
-We just knew each other?
But I was your one and only habibti.
Our relationship was
definitely incredibly serious.
You said it was 50-50 with Jinniya.
Don't tell me…
Ah.
[thunder rumbling]
Do you have an umbrella?
[Ka-young] An umbrella?
[thunderclap]
Wow, this woman sure is thorough.
It's raining. Kiss.
[Iblis] Hey, we're in Arabia.
[enthralling music playing]
But it's not raining here!
We broke that rule a long time ago.
You didn't buy it.
Man, I'm hungry.
Don't you have anything to eat?
-I almost used my third wish.
-[laughs sarcastically]
-Do it.
Yeah, right. Give me food!
[scoffs] You let me go hungry
all the time.
Dry up while I set the table.
Ah. Hmm.
Mm.
[gasps] This was here?
Wait. Hey, get rid of this right now.
No, burn it quickly. Let it rot!
Come on, this is…
[Ka-young]
Do I look similar to my past life?
What?
[soft music playing]
[Iblis] Yes.
You look similar.
Right?
I also think I look
exactly as I did in the hourglass.
So who's prettier? Me or her?
No, don't tell me.
No. Tell me.
-Oh, well--
-Never mind. It's me.
-[sighs]
-And what is that?
-[comical music plays]
-What?
What is?
[gulps]
Move over.
It's ramyeon.
Man, I told them to prepare
a proper Korean meal. [chuckles nervously]
-Hmm?
-[clinking]
Bring the fruit over.
What? Sure.
-[slurps]
-[dish clatters]
[Ka-young] Mm.
Mm.
So do you really waltz by yourself?
Without a partner?
-Waltz?
-[slurps]
I've never waltzed.
I don't know how.
Then why do they call the sand whirls
in the desert "a waltzing genie"?
Eh?
[cutlery clinking]
Moving on.
-Fine, then.
-Hmm?
Let's turn the legend into an actual fact.
[slurping softly]
Follow me. For old time's sake…
[cracking joints]
…let's tear it up.
Right.
[clears throat]
[soft ballad playing]
[Iblis] Mm? Mm?
There is a round ball
between the two of us right now.
That ball is a small universe.
The waltz is all about
maintaining that distance
while dancing around
an even larger universe.
-Do you understand?
-What? Yes.
Just let yourself fall under my spell.
Follow me in a trance.
Now left foot forward.
[in English] One, two, three.
-[in Korean] Back.
-Back.
[in English] One, two, three.
[in Korean] Forward.
[in English] One, two--
[in Korean] Are you going
to keep stepping on my feet?
This is a battle, not a dance.
How is it that whatever we do,
it becomes a duel?
And when exactly
did you fall under my spell?
Back.
[in English] One, two, three.
[in Korean] The second time I saw you?
But that was at the hotel.
Really?
That early on?
Yes. I knew the moment I saw you.
You come after the cars I fix.
-The adjustable wrenches I grip.
-[chuckles]
Let's stop. [grunts]
The wheels I roll.
-The hammers I use.
-I said stop. [grunts]
The crowbars I use.
The sound of dental scaling I like.
My auto shop, gamja-tang, Grandma,
Min-ji.
Sea louse…
[ballad continues playing]
[ballad fades]
[suspenseful music playing]
Pan-geum definitely made this.
Pan-geum, that bitch. She's here.
Gosh, why is this tooth
bothering me so much?
[winces] Gosh. [winces, groans]
[gasps]
What are you doing here, ma'am?
You'd better come clean.
Where is Pan-geum?
She's in Hawaii…
Don't give me that crap.
This tastes exactly like Pan-geum's work.
She's here, isn't she?
-[hisses]
-[gasps]
How dare you hide her away
while you con us!
Lead the way! I need to see her now!
Please let go of me.
Why are you doing this?
Tramp. Where do you think
you're going? Come here.
-That mole.
-[gasps]
Pan-geum has that mole there too.
What the hell is this?
Are you Pan-geum?
-Is that you, Pan-geum?
-No, I'm not!
-Oh dearie!
-Dearie!
Oh! You are! You are Pan-geum!
[screams] It's Pan-geum!
Heung-rye! Heung-rye!
Good heavens! How on earth
could something like this happen?
[Mi-ju] Heung-rye!
Heung-rye.
Please just hear me out. Please?
Let go, you wretched witch!
My Lord!
I was wondering where you hid her,
but you were Pan-geum all along?
What the hell did you do?
How the hell did you become so young?
I'll tell you everything.
So please don't tell anyone else!
You disgust me. Let go, you bitch!
Dear Lord!
[crying] Gosh, Heung-rye. Please!
[wailing]
[intense music playing]
[Wahid] What? That bitch is Oh Pan-geum?
[chuckles] So that's how
she kept her grandma hidden.
I see. That's how she used her wish.
Let's start
by getting rid of that old bitch
before she runs her mouth more.
Ishrun.
You know what to do, right?
[both speaking in English]
One, two, three.
Two, two, three.
[in Korean] Let's go home now.
I'll go and get changed.
Are my clothes dry?
Of course. [chuckles]
[in English] One, two, three. Two, two…
-[ominous music playing]
-One, two--
[ominous music continues playing]
-[yawns]
-[tense music playing]
[soft ballad playing]